A Guide to the Commonwealth Fund records, President, Karen Davis papers, SG 2 FA1127
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Meetings and Program Files, 5; 34.16 Cubic Feet
  - Medicare Legislation Colloquium, 2004 June 30 (Box 140, Folder 1077)
  - Transition Network Health Advisory Board, New York, 2004 June 24 (Box 140, Folder 1078)
  - Harvard University, 2004 May 16-21 (Box 140, Folder 1079)
  - Medicare's Future, Washington, D. C., 2004 May 17 (Box 140, Folder 1080)
  - Peterson Lecture, Chicago, 2004 May 15 (Box 140, Folder 1081)
  - Academic Health Center Quality Consortium, 2004 May 13 (Box 140, Folder 1082)
  - Carolina Health Care Summit, Raleigh, NC, 2004 May 9-11 (Box 141, Folder 1083)
  - New America Foundation Panel, Washington, D. C., 2004 May 20 (Box 141, Folder 1084)
  - Eleventh Annual Princeton Conference, Princeton, NJ, 2004 May 19-21 (Box 141, Folder 1085)
  - Medicare Research Agenda Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2004 May 17 (Box 141, Folder 1086)
  - VHA Annual Strategic Planning Meeting, Phoenix, AZ, 2004 April 20 (Box 141, Folder 1087)
  - International Network of Applied Health Services Researchers, New York, 2004 April 1-2 (Box 141, Folder 1088-1090)
  - Program Monitoring Committee Meeting, 2004 September 9 (Box 142, Folder 1091-1092)
  - Program Monitoring Committee, 1994-1998 (Box 142, Folder 1093)
  - Edward Brandt - Program Monitoring Committee, 1997-2001 (Box 142, Folder 1094)
  - Healthy Steps, 2001 (Box 143, Folder 1095)
  - Lewis Bernard Correspondence, 1993-2001 (Box 143, Folder 1096)
  - Experiences with Managed Care Study, 1995 (Box 143, Folder 1097)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 1998 (Box 143, Folder 1098)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 1999 (Box 143, Folder 1099)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2007 (Box 143, Folder 1100)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2008-2009 (Box 144, Folder 1101-1104)
  - Executive Management Meetings, 2009-2011 (Box 145, Folder 1105-1107)
  - Frances Cooke Macgregor, 1998-2001 (Box 146, Folder 1108)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Cycle, 2006 April (Box 146, Folder 1109)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Cycle, 2006 November (Box 146, Folder 1110)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Docket Phone Calls, 2007 April (Box 146, Folder 1111)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Retreat, Washington, D. C., 2007 April (Box 146, Folder 1112)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting, 2007 July 9-10 (Box 147, Folder 1113)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting, 2007 November 12-13 (Box 147, Folder 1114)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2004 (Box 147, Folder 1115)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2005 (Box 147, Folder 1116)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2006 (Box 147, Folder 1117)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2006 (Box 148, Folder 1117A)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2008-2009 (Box 148, Folder 1118)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2008 (Box 148, Folder 1119)
  - Foundation Executives Group (FEG) Meeting, 2009 (Box 148, Folder 1120-1121)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2003-2005 (Box 148, Folder 1122)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2006 (Box 149, Folder 1123)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2007 (Box 149, Folder 1124)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2008 (Box 149, Folder 1125)
  - Karen Davis Meeting Notes, 2009-2010 (Box 149, Folder 1126-1127)
  - International Symposium on Health Care Policy, Washington, D. C., 2003 October 22-24 (Box 150, Folder 1128)
  - Executive Management Team Retreat, 2004 August 18-19 (Box 150, Folder 1129-1130)
  - 2005 Task Force Meeting - Karen Davis Notes (Box 150, Folder 1131)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board of Directors Meeting and Retreat, Washington, D.C., 2005 April 11-12 (Box 150, Folder 1132)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Retreat, 2008 April 14-15 (Box 150, Folder 1133)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 July 14-15 (Box 150, Folder 1134)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board of Directors Meeting, 2008 November 10-11 (Box 150, Folder 1135)
  - Creating Consensus (Box 150, Folder 1136)
  - Policy Strategy (Box 150, Folder 1137)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System - Achieving-Reinvesting Savings Report (Box 151, Folder 1138)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System - Commission Framework Poll (Box 151, Folder 1139)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System Management (Box 151, Folder 1140)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System, Washington, D. C., 2005 November 29-30 (Box 151, Folder 1141)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System, 2005 July 20 (Box 151, Folder 1142)
  - State Scorecard (Box 151, Folder 1143)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System - Power-Point Slides, 2005 March 2 (Box 151, Folder 1144)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System, 2006 July 17-19 (Box 152, Folder 1146)
  - Commission on a High Performance Health System Retreat, 2006 June 7-8 (Box 152, Folder 1147-1148)
  - Congressional Staff Retreat, 2007 February (Box 152, Folder 1149)
  - Congressional Retreat, 2004 January 15-18 (Box 152, Folder 1150)
  - Congressional Retreat, Philadelphia, 2008 January 10-12 (Box 152, Folder 1151)
  - Commonwealth Fund Effeciency Group (Box 152, Folder 1152)
  - Commonwealth Fund International Working Group on Quality Indicators (Box 152, Folder 1153)
  - Pennyhill Conference, Bagshot, UK, 2007 July 13-15 (Box 152, Folder 1154)
  - Commonwealth Fund and the Nuffield Trust - Eleventh International Meeting on Quality of Health Care, Boston, 2010 July 16-18 (Box 153, Folder 1155)
  - IOM Quality Initiative Committee, 2004 August 3-4 (Box 153, Folder 1156)
  - Ellison Institute at Harvard University, Cuernavaca, Mexico - Notes, 2005 August 10-12 (Box 153, Folder 1157)
  - Foundation Executives Group, Pocantico, NY, 2005 May 12 (Box 153, Folder 1158)
  - ABIM Foundation Summer Forum, Colorado Springs, CO, 2006 July 29-August 1 (Box 153, Folder 1159)
  - IOM Health Policy Interest Group, 2008 October 12 (Box 153, Folder 1160)
  - IOM Health Policy Section Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2008 October 12 (Box 153, Folder 1161)
  - ISQua International Conference, Copenhagen, 2008 October 19-22 (Box 153, Folder 1162)
  - MedCom, Odense, DK, 2008 October 22 (Box 153, Folder 1163)
  - University of Florida, College of Public Health, Gainsville, FL, 2008 October 2-3 (Box 153, Folder 1164)
  - Forum of Executive Women Conference, Philadelphia, PA, 2007 May 17 (Box 153, Folder 1165)
  - Foundation Executives Group, Pocantico, NY, 2007 May 10-11 (Box 154, Folder 1166)
  - ABIM Foundation Forum, Montreal, 2007 August 4-7 (Box 154, Folder 1167)
  - Mayo Clinic Health Policy Center, Washington, D. C., 2007 October 9 (Box 154, Folder 1168)
  - IOM Annual Meeting, Washington, D. C., 2007 October 7-8 (Box 154, Folder 1169)
  - Century Foundation, Business and National Health Care Reform, Washington, D. C., 2007 September 14 (Box 154, Folder 1170)
  - C-Change Presentation, Kennebunkport, ME, 2007 September 3-4 (Box 154, Folder 1171)
  - IHA National Pay for Performance Summit, Los Angeles, 2008 February 27-29 (Box 154, Folder 1172)
  - Harvard-NEJM Symposium, Boston, 2008 September 12 (Box 154, Folder 1173)
  - ABIM Foundation Forum, Yountville Napa Valley, CA, 2008 July 26-29 (Box 154, Folder 1174)
  - Bassett-Commonwealth Fund Colloquium on Group Employee Models, Washington, D. C., 2009 September 16 (Box 154, Folder 1175)
  - VA Roundtable on Quality and Safety, Washington, D. C., 2009 April 28-29 (Box 155, Folder 1176)
  - Congressional Meetings, 2006 May 17 (Box 155, Folder 1177)
  - Congressional Meetings, 2006 May 10 (Box 155, Folder 1178)
  - Congressional Meetings, 2007 July 31-August 2 (Box 155, Folder 1179)
  - Congressional Meetings, 2006 July 26 (Box 155, Folder 1180)
  - Congressional Meetings, 2006 June 15 (Box 155, Folder 1181)
  - Congressional Meetings, 2006 June 14 (Box 155, Folder 1182)
  - ABC News Advisory Panel (Box 155, Folder 1183)
  - American Academy of Arts and Sciences (Box 155, Folder 1184)
  - AcademyHealth Annual Research Meeting, Orlando, 2007 June 3-5 (Box 155, Folder 1185)
  - AcademyHealth Interest Groups - State Health Research and Policy Meeting, Orlando, 2007 June 2 (Box 155, Folder 1186)
  - AcademyHealth 2009 National Health Policy Conference Advisory Committee (Box 155, Folder 1187)
  - National Health Policy Conference, Washington, D. C., 2006 February 6-7 (Box 155, Folder 1188)
  - AcademyHealth Council of Sponsors (Box 155, Folder 1189)
  - ABIM Foundation Forum, 2009 August (Box 156, Folder 1190)
  - Commission on A High Performance Health System - North Dakota Site Visit, 2007 July 18 (Box 156, Folder 1191)
  - Ideas for Change (Box 156, Folder 1192)
  - MEM (Box 156, Folder 1193)
  - Staff Meeting Talking Points, 1995-1998 (Box 156, Folder 1194)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting Follow-Up Notes, 1994-2008 (Box 157, Folder 1195-1197)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting, 2009 November 9-10 (Box 158, Folder 1198)
  - Commonwealth Fund Board Meeting, 2010 November 8-9 (Box 158, Folder 1199)
  - American Board of Internal Medicine (ABIM) Foundation, 2008 (Box 162, Folder 1224-1225)
  - Alliance of Community Health Plans (ACIP) (Box 162, Folder 1226)
  - Blue Cross Blue Shield of Massachusetts Advisory Council (Box 162, Folder 1227)
  - Foundation Executives Group, 2009 April 30-May 1 (Box 162, Folder 1228)
  - Congressional Budget Office (CBO) Health Advisory Panel, 2008 December 5 (Box 162, Folder 1229)
  - Congressional Budget Office (CBO) Health Advisory Panel, 2007-2008 (Box 163, Folder 1230-1232)
  - Center for Study of the Presidency (Box 163, Folder 1233)
  - Centers for Medicare and Medicaid Services (CMS) (Box 163, Folder 1234)
  - CEO Dinner, New York, 2008 November 11 (Box 163, Folder 1235)
  - Columbia University Mailman School of Public Health (Box 163, Folder 1236)
  - Columbia University School of Nursing, Board of Visitors (Box 163, Folder 1237)
  - Consumers Union (Box 163, Folder 1238)
  - Denver Health, 2006 (Box 163, Folder 1239)
  - Dirigo Health Reform Act (Box 164, Folder 1240)
  - Employee Benefit Research Institute (EBRI), 2006 (Box 164, Folder 1241)
  - Endowment for Health (Box 164, Folder 1242)
  - 2006 John Gardner Leadership Award Committee (Box 164, Folder 1243)
  - Eugene Garfield Award Research! America (Box 164, Folder 1244)
  - Garfield Award Committee (Box 164, Folder 1245)
  - Geisinger Health Systems Board of Directors (Box 164, Folder 1246)
  - GIH Working Group on Access and Coverage, 2004-2006 (Box 165, Folder 1247)